小馬鎮，我曾經愛著你
Ponyville, I was in love with you
但我想換換新模式
but I'm trying something new
反正不缺我一人
Ya don't need me now
我知道，聽來有點好過頭
I knew it was too good to be true
我知道我們都得輸
I knew that we'd both lose
而你也讓我失望
and you've let me down
是時候說再見
It's time to say goodbye
我學會了飛天
'cause I've learned how to fly
最近不是很想看到彼此
Don't wanna see you anytime soon
這裡沒有多少壓力
All tension's thin out here
覆蓋這冰冷的大氣
in this cool atmosphere
我看，我就活在這月球上
so, I'll be living here on the moon
La da da da da
La da da da da da
看看我，在這裡自己散步
Look at me, trottin' here on my own
看看我都飛了多遠
I mean, look how far I've flown
我已經習慣了這裡
It's already growing on me
現在想一想，我們再也不會見面
Come to think of it, you'll never see me again
連問好都不要問我
Don't even ask me how I've been
最好是不要想我
and don't even think about me
是時候說再見
It's time to say goodbye
我學會了飛天
'cause I've learned how to fly
最近不是很想看到彼此
Don't wanna see you anytime soon
這裡沒有多少壓力
All tension's thin out here
覆蓋這冰冷的大氣
in this cool atmosphere
我看，我就活在這月球上
so, I'll be living here on the moon
在這月球上
Here On The Moon
這不是什麼躲貓貓遊戲
This is no game of hide and seek
我估計是需要時間冷靜
I guess I just need time to think
所以，面對現實
So, face the facts
因為我不會回家
'Cause I won't be back
是時候說再見
It's time to say goodbye
我學會了飛天
'cause I've learned how to fly
最近不是很想看到彼此
Don't wanna see you anytime soon
這裡沒有多少壓力
All tension's thin out here
覆蓋這冰冷的大氣
in this cool atmosphere
我看，我就活在這月球上
so, I'll be living here on the moon
我不是在玩躲貓貓
I'm not playing hide and seek
只是需要自己思考
I just need time to think
所以我就在這月球上想一想
So I'll be thinking here on the moon
La da da da da
La da da da da da